[Team Leader Baek Su Jeong]
[قائد الفريق بايك سو جونغ]
[Mun Ka Young]
[نحن مازلنا شباب]
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[المخرج بان جو يون]
[Choi Hyun Wook]
[تشوي هيون ووك]
[Yongsung's successor. [New chaebol director?]
[خليفة يونغ سونغ. [مدير جديد لشركة تشايبول؟]
[Im Se Mi]
[إم سي مي]
[Kwak Si Yang]
[كواك سي يانغ]
[My Dearest Nemesis]
[عدوتي العزيزة]
[This drama is fiction.]
[هذه الدراما خيالية.]
[Characters and settings are fictitious.]
[الشخصيات والإعدادات خيالية.]
He's crazy.
إنه مجنون.
Why did he kiss me?
لماذا قبلني؟
I know he was drunk, but still.
أعرف أنه كان مخمورًا، ولكن لا يزال.
No matter how much I think,
بغض النظر عن مدى تفكيري،
there's only one reason.
هناك سبب واحد فقط
It's too late to get the dress dry-cleaned.
لقد فات الأوان لتنظيف الفستان.
You should just keep it.
يجب عليك فقط الاحتفاظ به
Pardon? Why?
عفوا؟ لماذا؟
I don't need it,
أنا لا أحتاج إليها
and it was pretty.
وكانت جميلة
Because the only one who'd give me
لأنه الشخص الوحيد الذي سيعطيني
chocolate milk is you, Ms. Baek.
حليب الشوكولاتة هو أنت، السيدة بايك.
He
هو
likes me.
يُحِبُّني
He should just tell me he likes me.
يجب عليه فقط أن يخبرني أنه يحبني
Why would he startle me by kissing first?
لماذا يفاجئني بتقبيله أولاً؟
How will he see me from now on?
كيف سيرى من الآن فصاعدا؟
Gosh. Since when did he like me?
يا إلهي، منذ متى كان يحبني؟
Was it
هل كان
from the beginning?
من البداية؟
Geez.
يا إلهي.
I stayed up all night.
لقد بقيت مستيقظا طوال الليل.
You woke up early.
لقد استيقظت مبكرا.
I couldn't sleep, more like.
لم أستطع النوم، على الأرجح.
You couldn't sleep?
لم تتمكن من النوم؟
No.
لا.
As you'd expect.
كما تتوقع.
He was too excited to sleep.
كان متحمسًا جدًا لدرجة أنه لم يتمكن من النوم.
How could he sleep after doing such a thing?
كيف يستطيع أن ينام بعد أن فعل مثل هذا الشيء؟
I tend to be picky with where I sleep.
أنا أميل إلى أن أكون انتقائيا فيما يتعلق بالمكان الذي أنام فيه.
An obvious excuse. Fine.
عذر واضح. حسنًا.
Oh, I see.
أوه، أرى.
You're the one who woke up early.
أنت من استيقظ مبكرا.
Did you not sleep well?
هل لم تنم جيدا؟
Me?
أنا؟
Well, no, I slept really well.
حسنًا، لا، لقد نمت جيدًا.
I'm a morning person, "Miracle Morning,"
أنا شخص صباحي، "صباح المعجزة"
a superior type like that.
نوع متفوق مثل هذا.
Superior type?
نوع متفوق؟
By chance,
بالصدفة
would you like to join me for a walk?
هل ترغب بالانضمام إلي في نزهة؟
Where?
أين؟
There's a nice place over there.
هناك مكان جميل هناك.
Why go to a nice place?
لماذا نذهب إلى مكان جميل؟
Will he confess his love?
هل سيعترف بحبه؟
He's confessing just like this?
إنه يعترف بهذه الطريقة؟
[Episode 6]
[الحلقة 6]
Gosh, what should I say?
يا إلهي، ماذا علي أن أقول؟
He won't give me a hard time at work
لن يجعلني أواجه صعوبة في العمل
for saying no, right?
لقولك لا، أليس كذلك؟
Why does he like me and make things difficult?
لماذا يحبني ويجعل الأمور صعبة؟
- So- - I'll give it a thought first.
- إذن- سأفكر في الأمر أولًا.
Pardon?
عفو؟
It's over there.
إنها هناك.
What do I do?
ماذا أفعل؟
He even chose a place to confess.
حتى أنه اختار مكانًا للاعتراف.
Aren't you coming?
ألا تأتي؟
I'm coming. Coming.
انا قادم. قادم.
[Yonghan Spring]
[ربيع يونغان]
He'll confess at a place like this?
سيعترف في مكان مثل هذا؟
Is this the nice place...
هل هذا المكان جميل؟
Yes.
نعم.
This is the spring CEO An mentioned yesterday.
هذا هو الرئيس التنفيذي الربيعي الذي ذكره أمس.
The water is tasty, and it's good for a hangover.
الماء لذيذ، وهو جيد لعلاج صداع الكحول.
[This spring has been around since 1392...]
[هذا الربيع موجود منذ عام 1392...]
It does taste good.
إن طعمه جيد.
Did we come here to drink spring water?
هل جئنا هنا لشرب مياه الينابيع؟
Why else would you come here?
لماذا تأتي إلى هنا إذن؟
Yes.
نعم.
There's no need to rush it.
ليست هناك حاجة للتسرع.
You should try some, too.
ينبغي عليك أن تجرب بعضًا منها أيضًا.
You came this far.
لقد وصلت إلى هذا الحد.
I should. I came this far.
يجب علي أن أفعل ذلك، لقد وصلت إلى هذه النقطة.
We're in it together.
نحن في ذلك معًا.
Should we say cheers?
هل يجب علينا أن نقول هتاف؟
It's cooling and sweet, right?
إنه بارد ولذيذ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, it's very invigorating.
نعم، إنه منشط جدًا.
Would you like more?
هل تريد المزيد؟
No, I can get it
لا، أستطيع الحصول عليه
Well...
حسنًا...
The thing is...
الشيء هو...
Pardon?
عفو؟
This is no good.
هذا ليس جيدا.
There...
هناك...
There's an annoying leaf here.
هناك ورقة مزعجة هنا.
This is no good.
هذا ليس جيدا.
Yongsung's successor should be in a beautiful place.
ينبغي أن يكون خليفة يونغسونغ في مكان جميل.
Let's go now.
دعنا نذهب الآن.
Wait...
انتظر...
What?
ماذا؟
Does he think this is a bathroom?
هل يظن أن هذا حمام؟
You made the right decision, CEO An.
لقد اتخذت القرار الصحيح، الرئيس التنفيذي آن.
You said you'd think about it, but you decided.
قلت أنك ستفكر في الأمر، ولكنك قررت.
Thank you for changing your mind.
شكرا لك على تغيير رأيك.
I'll make sure to pay you the margin.
سأتأكد من دفع الهامش لك.
We'll do our best to treat the customers well.
سنبذل قصارى جهدنا لمعاملة العملاء بشكل جيد.
It's okay. It's okay.
لا بأس، لا بأس.
I'll talk to the employees first
سأتحدث مع الموظفين أولاً
and sign the contract later.
وتوقيع العقد لاحقًا.
Gosh. Of course, they'll follow your decision.
يا إلهي، بالطبع سوف يتبعون قرارك.
On behalf of the Yongsung Department Store,
بالنيابة عن متجر يونغسونغ،
I'll make sure you don't regret the decision.
سأتأكد من أنك لن تندم على هذا القرار.
This is how silly he is.
إنه غبي بهذه الدرجة.
He was a scholarship student.
كان طالباً حاصلاً على منحة دراسية.
He is so devoted to the company.
إنه مخلص جدًا للشركة.
Hey, you're acting like the CEO.
مهلا، أنت تتصرف مثل الرئيس التنفيذي.
Stop acting cheeky.
توقف عن التصرف بوقاحة.
Ms. Baek.
السيدة بايك.
How dare you call noon a that
كيف تجرؤ على تسمية الظهر بهذا؟
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
لا بأس، لا بأس، لا بأس.
You're the grandson of the Yongsung chairwoman.
أنت حفيد رئيسة يونغسونغ.
He's basically the CEO.
إنه الرئيس التنفيذي بشكل أساسي.
I figured you go to the spring yourself
اعتقدت أنك ستذهب إلى الربيع بنفسك
rather than asking someone.
بدلا من سؤال شخص ما.
So, I got some for you.
لذلك، حصلت على بعض لك.
I get that you don't want to disappoint your grandson,
أفهم أنك لا تريد أن تخيب أمل حفيدك،
but you should use your subordinates sometimes.
لكن يجب عليك استخدام مرؤوسيك في بعض الأحيان.
Considering your age,
بالنظر إلى عمرك،
you might hurt your back.
ربما تؤذي ظهرك.
Listen to you.
استمع اليك.
I take back the compliment.
أتراجع عن المجاملة.
Do you think I'd be moved by this
هل تعتقد أنني سأتأثر بهذا؟
and sign a contract?
وتوقيع العقد؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
I'm not that naive.
أنا لست ساذجة إلى هذه الدرجة.
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[المخرج بان جو يون]
I wish you kept it a secret until the end.
أتمنى أن تبقي الأمر سرا حتى النهاية.
Why are you revealing yourself now?
لماذا تكشف عن نفسك الآن؟
We need to trust each other to work together.
نحن بحاجة إلى الثقة ببعضنا البعض للعمل معًا.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you from the beginning.
أنا آسف لأنني لم أتمكن من إخبارك منذ البداية.
That's how much I wanted you to hear me out.
لقد أردت بشدة أن تسمعني.
Chairwoman Jung
رئيسة اللجنة يونغ
cares more about the company than herself.
يهتم بالشركة أكثر من نفسه.
She can do anything for Yongsung.
إنها قادرة على فعل أي شيء من أجل يونغسونغ.
She knows corporations benefit from a better society.
إنها تعلم أن الشركات تستفيد من مجتمع أفضل.
As her grandson,
كحفيدها،
I'm carrying out my grandmother's will.
أنا أنفذ وصية جدتي.
If you sign with us, through the foundation,
إذا قمت بالتوقيع معنا من خلال المؤسسة،
we'll invest in Ganghan Farm's hospital charity
سنستثمر في مستشفى Ganghan Farm الخيري
and the construction of the ice cream factory.
وإنشاء مصنع الآيس كريم.
Do you mean that?
هل تقصد ذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
I want those children to be healthy
أريد أن يكون هؤلاء الأطفال أصحاء
like your grandson someday.
مثل حفيدك يوما ما.
I mean everything.
أعني كل شيء.
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[المخرج بان جو يون]
Director said that?
المخرج قال ذلك؟
Yes. As you said,
نعم كما قلت
if it'd go to someone else anyway,
إذا كان الأمر سيذهب إلى شخص آخر على أي حال،
it'd be better if I spent the profit well.
سيكون من الأفضل لو أنفقت الربح جيدًا.
I'd be happy if you'd do all that.
سوف أكون سعيدًا إذا فعلت كل ذلك.
Yes.
نعم.
We'll get going now, then.
سوف نبدأ الآن، إذن.
Okay. Right, take this with you.
حسنًا، خذ هذا معك.
These are our products
هذه هي منتجاتنا
and I packed some doraji and godeulbbaegi.
وقمت بتعبئة بعض الدوراجي والغوديولبايجي.
I saw you enjoying them yesterday.
لقد رأيتك تستمتع بها بالأمس.
- Take them. - Me?
- خذهم. - أنا؟
Of course. You both liked them.
Of course. You both liked them.
Take this, too.
Take this, too.
It was worth coming this far.
It was worth coming this far.
The suggestion you made to CEO An...
The suggestion you made to CEO An...
Since when did you think about doing that?
Since when did you think about doing that?
You're the one who made me come up with the idea.
You're the one who made me come up with the idea.
You made me come this far.
You made me come this far.
Last night...
Last night...
Yes?
Yes?
So, last night...
So, last night...
Last night.
Last night.
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh!
Will he finally tell me now?
Will he finally tell me now?
Are you hot? I have the AC on.
Are you hot? I have the AC on.
No, I'm okay.
No, I'm okay.
I'm all ready. Tell me.
I'm all ready. Tell me.
Ready for what?
Ready for what?
You worked hard last night.
You worked hard last night.
Is that it?
Is that it?
And if you're okay
And if you're okay
If I'm okay?
If I'm okay?
If you're okay, would you like to
If you're okay, would you like to
listen to my music?
listen to my music?
Yes.
Yes.
Sure, go ahead.
Sure, go ahead.
Play the song I was listening to.
Play the song I was listening to.
I'll play Crackshot's "Follow Me."
I'll play Crackshot's "Follow Me."
♫ Follow, follow, follow, follow me ♫
♫ Follow, follow, follow, follow me ♫
♫ For a while, I've been watching you ♫
♫ For a while, I've been watching you ♫
♫ It's okay to be awkward ♫
♫ It's okay to be awkward ♫
♫ Let the music carry your body ♫
♫ Let the music carry your body ♫
♫ It gets cold when the morning comes ♫
♫ It gets cold when the morning comes ♫
♫ The light that shines on today ♫
♫ The light that shines on today ♫
When will he talk to me, anyway?
When will he talk to me, anyway?
♫ Like this. Like this. ♫
♫ Like this. Like this. ♫
♫ Tonight. It's party time. ♫
♫ Tonight. It's party time. ♫
♫ Follow, follow, follow, follow me ♫
♫ Follow, follow, follow, follow me ♫
I'll let you go in now.
I'll let you go in now.
Will you really leave like this?
Will you really leave like this?
I forgot something important.
I forgot something important.
That's it, right?
That's it, right?
See you on Monday.
See you on Monday.
What do you mean, that's it?
What do you mean, that's it?
What happened last night. Will you...
What happened last night. Will you...
Will you just let it slide?
Will you just let it slide?
You should explain yourself or something.
You should explain yourself or something.
It's already in the past. Is it necessary?
It's already in the past. Is it necessary?
Let go of small mistakes like that.
Let go of small mistakes like that.
Mistake?
Mistake?
Yes, a mistake we made while we were drunk.
Yes, a mistake we made while we were drunk.
Wasn't it the same to you?
Wasn't it the same to you?
Right.
Right.
Mistake.
Mistake.
It was a mistake and an accident.
It was a mistake and an accident.
I'm not that crazy of a person.
I'm not that crazy of a person.
As you know,
As you know,
I don't think of you as a man at all.
I don't think of you as a man at all.
Why would you suddenly say that?
Why would you suddenly say that?
Did I beg you to think of me as a man?
Did I beg you to think of me as a man?
I would've forgiven you if you begged.
I would've forgiven you if you begged.
What?
What?
I look manly.
I look manly.
He's crazy.
He's crazy.
Ignore a mistake like that?
Ignore a mistake like that?
He kisses when he's drunk. He's the player.
He kisses when he's drunk. He's the player.
Why is she angry, exactly?
Why is she angry, exactly?
The makgeolli.
The makgeolli.
It doesn't go well with me.
It doesn't go well with me.
I fell asleep waiting for her call.
I fell asleep waiting for her call.
She left me alone that night.
She left me alone that night.
Am I not the one who should be angry?
Am I not the one who should be angry?
Su Jeong.
Su Jeong.
Su Jeong?
Su Jeong?
Hey, Dad. Did you call me?
Hey, Dad. Did you call me?
You skipped dinner. What are you doing?
You skipped dinner. What are you doing?
The door is acting up.
The door is acting up.
You don't even use it.
You don't even use it.
I'm just
I'm just
a bit angry,
a bit angry,
but I can't blast someone's head.
but I can't blast someone's head.
Why?
Why?
Is it noisy? Should I stop?
Is it noisy? Should I stop?
No, no. It's okay. Go ahead.
No, no. It's okay. Go ahead.
Do whatever you want to do, sweetheart.
Do whatever you want to do, sweetheart.
Okay.
Okay.
Yes, I'm the same.
Yes, I'm the same.
I was drunk by the alcohol and atmosphere and ki
I was drunk by the alcohol and atmosphere and ki
That's no big deal.
That's no big deal.
It was just a mistake of one night.
It was just a mistake of one night.
Yes.
Yes.
Mistake?
Mistake?
Shouldn't he apologize if he made a mistake?
Shouldn't he apologize if he made a mistake?
- Yes. - How can you sleep right now?
- Yes. - How can you sleep right now?
Ms. Baek?
Ms. Baek?
Is something going on at work?
Is something going on at work?
Something's going on with us two.
هناك شيء يحدث معنا.
I just can't believe what's going on.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق ما يحدث.
What happened yesterday... I mean, the day before.
ما حدث بالأمس... أعني، اليوم السابق
Can you just call it a mistake and move on?
هل يمكنك أن تسميها خطأ وتمضي قدمًا؟
What should I call it, then?
ماذا يجب أن أسميه إذن؟
I'm being understanding. Why are you angry?
أنا متفهم، لماذا أنت غاضب؟
You're being understanding?
هل أنت متفهم؟
Yes.
نعم
You drank makgeolli by mistake
لقد شربت ماكجولي بالخطأ
and we spent the night at the farm.
وقضينا الليل في المزرعة.
I'm letting it go because it was a mistake.
سأترك الأمر لأنه كان خطأً.
I'm being understanding. Very much so.
أنا متفهمة للغاية.
That's not what I'm talking about.
هذا ليس ما أتحدث عنه.
Are you talking about that, then?
هل تتحدث عن ذلك إذن؟
Is it because you feel bad?
هل هذا لأنك تشعر بالسوء؟
Apologize if you feel bad.
اعتذر إذا كنت تشعر بالسوء.
Don't get angry.
لا تغضب .
Seriously.
بجد.
Are you telling me to apologize?
هل تطلب مني الإعتذار؟
Should I, then?
هل يجب علي ذلك إذن؟
You should since
يجب عليك منذ ذلك الحين
you disappeared while drinking together.
لقد اختفيتما بينما كنتما تشربان معًا.
How could you leave someone who fell asleep
كيف يمكنك ترك شخص نام؟
waiting for you?
في انتظارك
I was so shocked when I woke up.
لقد صدمت كثيرا عندما استيقظت
I was cold, achy, and the bugs...
كنت أشعر بالبرد، والألم، والحشرات...
It was unbelievable.
كان الأمر لا يصدق
That's why I couldn't sleep well.
لهذا السبب لم أتمكن من النوم جيدًا
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
I'll be understanding and let this go, too.
سأكون متفهمًا وسأترك هذا الأمر أيضًا.
Or did something else happen?
أم حدث شيء آخر؟
Nothing happened.
لم يحدث شيء.
He doesn't
هو لا يفعل
remember.
يتذكر.
He's not a man. He's the same age as Su Bin.
إنه ليس رجلاً، إنه في نفس عمر سو بين
How could I think of him as a man?
كيف يمكنني أن أفكر فيه كرجل؟
Thinking now, she said that back then, too.
أفكر الآن، لقد قالت ذلك في ذلك الوقت أيضًا.
On top of treating me like a little brother all day.
علاوة على معاملتي كأخ صغير طوال اليوم.
But why?
ولكن لماذا؟
Why doesn't she think of me as a man?
لماذا لا تفكر بي كرجل؟
One million and twenty-one.
مليون وواحد وعشرون.
She doesn't think of me as a man.
إنها لا تفكر بي كرجل.
One million and twenty-two.
مليون واثنان وعشرون.
- She doesn't... - One million and twenty-three.
- هي لا... - مليون وثلاثة وعشرون.
She doesn't think of me...
إنها لا تفكر بي...
You finally reached a million after three years.
لقد وصلت أخيرا إلى المليون بعد ثلاث سنوات.
You worked very hard.
لقد عملت بجد.
One million and twenty-four.
مليون وأربعة وعشرون.
Let's count from the beginning.
دعونا نحسب من البداية.
My next goal is two years.
هدفي القادم هو عامين.
Two years.
سنتين.
She doesn't think of me as a man.
إنها لا تفكر بي كرجل.
- One. - She does think of me as a man.
- واحد. - إنها تفكر بي كرجل.
Why doesn't she think of me as a man?
لماذا لا تفكر بي كرجل؟
Do I need to know what it means to be a man?
هل أحتاج أن أعرف ماذا يعني أن أكون رجلاً؟
Chief Kwon,
الزعيم كوان
you met your husband at your previous job.
لقد قابلت زوجك في وظيفتك السابقة.
He's a year younger than you.
إنه أصغر منك بسنة.
Y-Yes, so?
ن-نعم، إذن؟
When did you start
متى بدأت؟
thinking of him as a man?
تفكر فيه كرجل؟
Well, he was good at his job and
حسنًا، لقد كان جيدًا في عمله و
I'm already perfect at that.
أنا مثالي بالفعل في ذلك.
He spent money generously on me.
لقد أنفق عليّ المال بسخاء.
That's too easy.
هذا سهل للغاية.
Is that it?
هل هذا هو؟
He was very thoughtful.
لقد كان عميق التفكير.
Yes, that was the biggest factor.
نعم، كان هذا هو العامل الأكبر.
I already do that, too.
أنا أفعل ذلك بالفعل أيضاً.
But that was out of the blue.
ولكن ذلك كان فجأة.
You never asked me any personal questions.
لم تسألني أي أسئلة شخصية أبدًا.
Did something happen over
هل حدث شيء ما في هذا الوقت؟
the weekend?
نهاية الاسبوع؟
It was a professional question.
لقد كان سؤالا مهنيا.
Knowing you well is a part of my job, too.
إن معرفتك جيدًا هي جزء من وظيفتي أيضًا.
Anyway, that's what you liked about him.
على أية حال، هذا ما أعجبك فيه.
It's simple.
إنه بسيط.
He was good at his job and...
لقد كان جيدًا في عمله و...
He spent money generously on me.
لقد أنفق عليّ المال بسخاء.
He was very thoughtful.
لقد كان عميق التفكير
Yes, that was the biggest factor.
نعم، كان هذا هو العامل الأكبر.
Let's all check ourselves in the mirror.
دعونا جميعا ننظر لأنفسنا في المرآة.
[Yongsung Department Store Renewal Info]
[معلومات تجديد متجر يونجسونج]
It's a shame just to use it as a lounge area.
من العار أن يتم استخدامه فقط كمنطقة صالة.
Wouldn't it have a bigger role
ألا يكون لها دور أكبر؟
in attracting new customers?
في جذب عملاء جدد؟
Yes, it'd be a shame not to utilize it.
نعم، سيكون من العار عدم الاستفادة منه.
Wow. You really have a good sense, Director.
واو، لديك حقًا حس جيد، يا مدير.
What do you think, Team Leader Baek?
ماذا تعتقد يا قائد الفريق بايك؟
It sounds like a good idea.
يبدو وكأنه فكرة جيدة.
I'll think about how we could use it.
سأفكر في كيفية استخدامه.
Sounds good.
ًيبدو جيدا.
You haven't had lunch yet, right?
لم تتناولي الغداء بعد، أليس كذلك؟
Pardon?
عفو؟
Yes.
نعم.
Let's go to the Yongsung Hotel next door, then.
دعونا نذهب إلى فندق يونغسونغ المجاور، إذن.
You have the renewal project on top of everything.
لديك مشروع التجديد على رأس كل شيء.
You're all working a lot.
أنتم جميعا تعملون كثيرا.
I'll treat you to today's lunch for that reason.
سأدعوك لتناول الغداء اليوم لهذا السبب.
This is Yongsung Hotel's pride,
هذا هو فخر فندق يونغسونغ،
The S-class Buffet.
بوفيه الفئة S.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Help yourselves, everyone.
ساعدوا أنفسكم جميعًا.
I prepared a lobster dish per person.
لقد قمت بإعداد طبق جراد البحر لكل شخص.
How much does all this cost?
كم يكلف كل هذا؟
It's at least 100,000 won per person.
يبلغ الحد الأدنى 100 ألف وون للشخص الواحد.
He really must be the chairwoman's grandson.
لا بد أن يكون حفيد رئيسة اللجنة حقًا.
He's using the chefs like his personal chefs.
إنه يستخدم الطهاة كما لو كانوا طهاته الشخصيين.
Geez, and he works hard, too?
يا إلهي، وهو يعمل بجد أيضًا؟
Gosh, I desperately want to get involved with him.
يا إلهي، أريد بشدة أن أرتبط به.
He'll be more popular than Chief Kim
سيكون أكثر شعبية من الرئيس كيم
from the design team.
من فريق التصميم.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I thought Director Ban was unfriendly.
اعتقدت أن المخرج بان كان غير ودود.
But he knows how to do this, too.
لكنّه يعرف كيف يفعل هذا أيضًا.
He seems like a workaholic who doesn't date.
يبدو وكأنه مدمن عمل لا يحب المواعدة.
Whoever gets him would be striking gold, right?
من يحصل عليه سوف يحقق ربحًا عظيمًا، أليس كذلك؟
Why are you suddenly telling me that?
لماذا تقول لي ذلك فجأة؟
You agree with each other often
تتفقون مع بعضكم البعض في كثير من الأحيان
and you seemed to get along.
ويبدو أنكما تتفقان.
I wondered if you were seeking a class upgrade.
لقد تساءلت عما إذا كنت تسعى إلى ترقية صفك.
I didn't think you were that type.
لم أكن أعتقد أنك من هذا النوع.
Of course, I'm not that type.
بالطبع، أنا لست من هذا النوع.
The director is just a boss to me.
المخرج بالنسبة لي مجرد رئيس.
I never considered him as a boyfriend or husband.
لم أعتبره أبدًا صديقًا أو زوجًا.
You can consider me, then.
يمكنك أن تفكر بي، إذن.
You're the strategy team leader.
أنت قائد فريق الإستراتيجية.
But you lack creativity.
لكنك تفتقر إلى الإبداع.
Enjoy.
استمتع
Thank you, Director.
شكرا لك يا مدير.
Lack creativity?
هل تفتقر إلى الإبداع؟
He should worry about his memory.
ينبغي عليه أن يقلق بشأن ذاكرته.
- Yes, Unni. - Can you talk?
- نعم أوني. - هل تستطيعين التحدث؟
Nothing happened last weekend, right?
لم يحدث شيء في نهاية الأسبوع الماضي، أليس كذلك؟
- Like what? - I was wondering
- مثل ماذا؟ - كنت أتساءل
if anything happened on the way home.
إذا حدث أي شيء في طريق العودة إلى المنزل.
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
Nothing would happen with that shitty, stupid player.
لن يحدث شيء مع هذا اللاعب الغبي والسخيف.
You said he didn't seem bad.
قلت أنه لا يبدو سيئا.
Are you back to normal now?
هل عدت إلى طبيعتك الآن؟
I added the "shitty, stupid" part.
لقد أضفت الجزء "السخيف والغبي".
What? Is that why you called?
ماذا؟ هل هذا هو السبب الذي جعلك تتصل؟
No.
لا.
Do you want to go on a blind date?
هل تريد الذهاب في موعد أعمى؟
There's a great match for you.
هناك مباراة رائعة بالنسبة لك.
He's older, and he's a lawyer.
إنه أكبر سناً، وهو محامي.
He's understanding, dependable, and sweet.
إنه متفهم، جدير بالثقة، ولطيف.
He's totally your type.
إنه نوعك تمامًا.
You'd better not say no.
من الأفضل أن لا تقول لا.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
Hey!
يا!
You! You! You little brat!
أنت! أنت! أيها الطفل الصغير!
You go on a date instead.
تذهب في موعد بدلا من ذلك.
Seriously! Gosh.
بجدية! يا إلهي.
You little...
أنت صغيرتي...
It hurts! I said I don't want to.
إنه يؤلمني! لقد قلت أنني لا أريد ذلك.
You're so immature.
أنت غير ناضجة جدًا.
That's why you divorced as soon as you married.
لهذا السبب قمت بالطلاق فور زواجك.
You're the same. You two. Seriously...
أنتما نفس الشيء، أنتما الاثنان، بجدية...
Why suddenly a blind date?
لماذا فجأة موعد أعمى؟
Team Leader.
قائد الفريق.
Are you going on a blind date?
هل أنت ذاهب في موعد أعمى؟
Great idea, Team Leader.
فكرة رائعة يا قائد الفريق.
How old is he?
كم عمره؟
What's his occupation? Hold on.
ما هي مهنته؟ انتظر.
He can't just have any job to be your match.
لا يمكنه أن يحصل على أي وظيفة ليكون منافساً لك.
Is he handsome? He's tall, too, right?
هل هو وسيم؟ إنه طويل القامة أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
How tall is he?
كم طوله؟
You need to check without shoes.
يجب عليك التحقق بدون حذاء.
I haven't decided. I don't know yet
لم أقرر بعد، لا أعلم بعد
Who's going on a blind date?
من سيذهب في موعد أعمى؟
Team Leader is.
قائد الفريق هو.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
I asked if it was true.
سألت إذا كان هذا صحيحا.
Why do you want to know?
لماذا تريد أن تعرف؟
D-Don't worry, Director.
د-لا تقلق يا مدير.
She won't slack off just because she's dating.
إنها لن تتهاون فقط لأنها تواعد.
- Right? - Director.
-صحيح؟ - المخرج.
The Chairwoman wants to see you.
تريد رئيسة اللجنة رؤيتك.
Team Leader Baek,
قائد الفريق بايك
talk to me briefly before you leave for the day.
تحدث معي لفترة وجيزة قبل أن تغادر في هذا اليوم.
He looked happy earlier. How strange.
لقد بدا سعيدًا في وقت سابق. كم هو غريب.
Congratulations.
مبروك.
The dream of your life will come true soon.
حلم حياتك سوف يتحقق قريبا.
She told us to completely expose you to the media.
لقد طلبت منا أن نكشفكم بالكامل أمام وسائل الإعلام.
She's trying to make you the official successor.
إنها تحاول أن تجعلك الخليفة الرسمي.
I thought she'd wait for the renewal result.
اعتقدت أنها ستنتظر نتيجة التجديد.
It's sooner than I thought.
لقد كان أسرع مما كنت أعتقد.
I think she's preparing ahead since it's going well.
أعتقد أنها تستعد مسبقًا لأن الأمور تسير على ما يرام.
Actually, when I was reporting to her,
في الواقع، عندما كنت أبلغها،
she asked me about you.
سألتني عنك.
What I thought watching you closely.
ما اعتقدته هو أنني أراقبك عن كثب.
She asked if you're only focusing on work.
سألتك إذا كنت تركز فقط على العمل.
Since Yongsung is her life,
وبما أن يونغسونغ هي حياتها،
she wants the successor to be the same.
إنها تريد أن يكون الخليفة هو نفسه.
So, what did you tell her?
إذن ماذا قلت لها؟
I told her the truth.
لقد قلت لها الحقيقة.
That no one focuses only on work like you.
لا أحد يركز فقط على العمل مثلك.
You can just keep doing what you've been doing.
بإمكانك الاستمرار في فعل ما كنت تفعله.
I guess so.
اعتقد ذلك.
I was thinking you and I are similar.
كنت أفكر أنك وأنا متشابهان.
The director is just a boss to me.
المخرج بالنسبة لي مجرد رئيس
I never considered him as a boyfriend or husband.
لم أعتبره أبدًا صديقًا أو زوجًا
I hope I don't get disappointed.
آمل أن لا أشعر بخيبة الأمل.
Like I was before.
كما كنت من قبل
I wasted time on silly stuff.
لقد ضيعت وقتي على أشياء سخيفة.
Wake up, Ban Ju Yeon.
استيقظي بان جو يون.
Don't make another mistake.
لا ترتكب خطأ آخر.
It's well summarized.
لقد تم تلخيصه بشكل جيد.
That's it for the day.
هذا كل شيء لهذا اليوم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Aren't you going home, Team Leader?
ألن تذهب إلى المنزل يا قائد الفريق؟
I'll stop by the director's office first.
سأتوقف عند مكتب المدير أولاً.
Huh?
هاه؟
He won't yell at you about the blind date, right?
لن يصرخ عليك بشأن الموعد الأعمى، أليس كذلك؟
No way. It must be something else.
لا يمكن، لابد أن يكون هناك شيء آخر.
Right. Doesn't sound right.
حسنًا، لا يبدو الأمر صحيحًا.
Unless he's interested in you. Yes.
ما لم يكن مهتمًا بك، نعم.
Right?
يمين؟
Yes. I'll get going now, then.
نعم، سأذهب الآن.
See you.
أرك لاحقًا.
Jun Su!
جون سو!
Jun Su.
جون سو.
Can I help you with something?
هل يمكنني مساعدتك بشيء ما؟
A man
رجل
visited a woman late to warn her about a womanizer.
زار امرأة في وقت متأخر لتحذيرها من رجل زير نساء.
Why would he do that?
لماذا يفعل ذلك؟
He's interested.
إنه مهتم.
And getting angry because I don't see him as a man?
وأغضب لأنني لا أراه رجلاً؟
- It's 100%. - How about kissing while drunk?
- إنها 100٪. - ماذا عن التقبيل أثناء السكر؟
And he forgot about it.
ونسي الأمر.
This isn't about you, right?
هذا لا يتعلق بك، أليس كذلك؟
No, it isn't.
لا، ليس كذلك.
I'm talking about an anime. A romance anime.
أنا أتحدث عن أنمي، أنمي رومانسي.
I read it recently.
قرأته مؤخرا.
I can't understand the male lead's psychology.
لا أستطيع أن أفهم نفسية البطل الذكر.
I was wondering if you can.
كنت أتساءل إذا كان بإمكانك.
Do you read anime, too? Are we having a pop-up?
هل تقرأ الأنمي أيضًا؟ هل لدينا نافذة منبثقة؟
You think I always work?
هل تعتقد أنني أعمل دائمًا؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
Your hobby is self-improvement. That's why.
هوايتك هي تحسين الذات. لهذا السبب.
Never mind, then.
لا بأس إذن.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
it's too obvious.
إنه واضح جدًا.
It's a cliche. A cliche.
إنها عبارة مبتذلة. عبارة مبتذلة.
The fact that he kissed.
حقيقة أنه قبل.
He couldn't have actually forgotten.
لم يكن بإمكانه أن ينسى فعليا.
He's pretending like he did.
إنه يتظاهر كما فعل.
Why is he pretending to have forgotten?
لماذا يتظاهر بالنسيان؟
In case he gets rejected.
في حالة رفضه.
Male leads don't have the courage to speak first.
لا يملك الرجال القادة الشجاعة للتحدث أولاً.
That's just how it is.
هكذا هو الأمر.
You can go home.
يمكنك الذهاب إلى المنزل.
Okay. See you.
حسنا، إلى اللقاء.
No wonder. I knew something was strange.
لا عجب، لقد عرفت أن هناك شيئًا غريبًا.
I didn't think he was like this.
لم أكن أعتقد أنه كان هكذا.
But he had no courage, huh?
ولكنه لم يكن لديه الشجاعة، أليس كذلك؟
Come in.
ادخل.
You wanted to see me before I left.
أردت رؤيتي قبل أن أغادر.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Are you concerned that I'm going on a blind date?
هل أنت قلق من أنني سأذهب في موعد أعمى؟
So, I can't date anyone?
لذا، لا أستطيع مواعدة أي شخص؟
No. As Deputy Yang said,
لا، كما قال النائب يانغ،
dating won't stop you from working hard.
لن يمنعك المواعدة من العمل الجاد.
I don't worry.
لا تقلق.
It's none of my business as your boss, either.
هذا لا يعنيني كرئيس لك أيضًا.
You can just be honest.
يمكنك فقط أن تكون صادقا.
How could I be more honest?
كيف يمكنني أن أكون أكثر صدقا؟
Pardon?
عفو؟
Then
ثم
why did you come all the way to my house?
لماذا أتيت إلى منزلي؟
You told me not to date Chief Kim.
لقد طلبت مني ألا أواعد الرئيس كيم.
Because you really have to watch out for players.
لأنه عليك حقًا الحذر من اللاعبين.
So, I was warning you.
لقد كنت أحذرك.
Anyone would've stopped you.
كان أي شخص سيوقفك.
I was just being nice. Don't get the wrong idea.
لقد كنت لطيفًا فقط. لا تفهمني خطأً.
The Chairwoman
رئيسة مجلس الإدارة
praised you for signing with the Ganghan Farm.
أشاد بك لتوقيعك مع مزرعة جانجان.
You'll hear good news during the salary negotiation.
سوف تسمع أخبارًا جيدة أثناء التفاوض على الراتب.
You'll receive a bonus, too.
وسوف تحصل على مكافأة أيضًا.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
هذا ما أردت أن أخبرك به.
Aren't you happy?
هل أنت غير سعيد؟
You said money makes you happy instantly.
لقد قلت أن المال يجعلك سعيدًا على الفور.
I'm happy.
انا سعيد.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You can leave.
يمكنك المغادرة.
Am I mistaken?
هل انا مخطئ؟
Does this mean I got it all mixed up?
هل هذا يعني أنني خلطت كل شيء؟
[He Kisses for 6,000 Won]
[يقبل مقابل 6000 وون]
You must kiss people to be nice.
يجب عليك تقبيل الناس لكي تكون لطيفًا.
- Kiss? - Yes.
- قبلة؟ - نعم.
You got drunk and kissed me.
لقد سكرت وقبلتني.
Am I still mistaken?
هل مازلت مخطئا؟
Didn't you confuse me?
لم تربكني؟
I apologize if I did.
أعتذر إذا فعلت ذلك.
He's apologizing now?
هل يعتذر الآن؟
But
لكن
should you be so angry about that?
هل يجب عليك أن تغضب من هذا الأمر؟
- Pardon? - By chance, did you
- عفواً؟ - بالصدفة، هل فعلت ذلك؟
enjoy that kiss?
هل تستمتع بهذه القبلة؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
This. I wanted to give it back.
هذا. أردت أن أعيده.
What's the money for?
ما هو المال من أجل؟
Think of it as a rental fee.
فكر في الأمر باعتباره رسوم إيجار.
Although I didn't want it.
رغم أنني لم أرغب في ذلك.
And don't ever recommend cartoons like this to me.
ولا تنصحوني أبدًا بأفلام كرتون مثل هذه.
It's so childish.
إنه أمر طفولي جدًا.
You learned about relationships this way.
لقد تعلمت عن العلاقات بهذه الطريقة.
No wonder you got dumped by your first love.
لا عجب أنك تخلى عنك حبك الأول.
If an adult keeps reading stuff like this,
إذا استمر شخص بالغ في قراءة أشياء مثل هذه،
you'd keep getting dumped.
سوف تستمر في التعرض للإهمال.
You'd get dumped forever.
سيتم التخلي عنك إلى الأبد.
I didn't tell you that to be mocked like this.
لم أخبرك بهذا حتى يتم السخرية منك بهذه الطريقة.
I'm also warning you to be nice.
أنا أيضا أحذرك من أن تكون لطيفا.
I'm being nice.
أنا لطيف.
Take it.
خذها.
I don't want money from someone
لا أريد المال من أحد
who doesn't understand its value.
من لا يفهم قيمتها
You're the one who should improve your taste.
أنت من يجب عليه تحسين ذوقك.
Because you have such poor taste,
لأن لديك ذوق سيء،
you got scammed by your first love.
لقد تعرضت للاحتيال من قبل حبك الأول.
The kiss?
القبلة؟
I didn't like it.
لم يعجبني ذلك.
I didn't like it. There's no way I did!
لم يعجبني هذا الأمر، لا يوجد أي طريقة تجعلني أحبه!
[My Strawberry]
[فراولتي]
- Unni. - Yes, Su Jeong.
- أوني. - نعم، سو جونغ.
I want to go on that blind date.
أريد أن أذهب إلى هذا الموعد الأعمى.
What?
ماذا؟
You want to go on a blind date?
هل تريد الذهاب في موعد أعمى؟
Yes.
نعم.
At this rate,
بهذا المعدل،
I don't think they'd grow any closer.
لا أعتقد أنهم سوف يقتربون أكثر.
She's back to the boss-hating employee again.
لقد عادت مرة أخرى إلى الموظفة التي تكره رئيسها.
We won't have to worry anymore.
لن نحتاج للقلق بعد الآن.
I would've done nothing if I had known.
لن أفعل شيئا لو كنت أعلم.
Ms. Baek would hate me for no reason.
السيدة بايك ستكرهني بلا سبب.
Anyway, it's a relief.
على أية حال، إنه أمر مريح.
They won't get hurt again.
لن يتعرضوا للأذى مرة أخرى.
But why have you been working here since earlier?
ولكن لماذا كنت تعمل هنا منذ وقت سابق؟
You followed me to the market last time.
لقد تبعتني إلى السوق في المرة الماضية.
Using this as an excuse, I wanted to help
باستخدام هذا كذريعة، أردت المساعدة
and gain brownie points from you.
واحصل على نقاط براوني منك.
What would you want brownie points from me?
ما هي النقاط البراونية التي تريدها مني؟
Did you forget I confessed my feelings to you?
هل نسيت أنني اعترفت لك بمشاعري؟
Oh, that?
أوه، هذا؟
Did you forget I said no?
هل نسيت أنني قلت لا؟
They say the third time is the charm.
يقولون أن المرة الثالثة هي السحر.
I thought you were cooler than this.
اعتقدت أنك أكثر برودة من هذا.
I thought I was, too.
اعتقدت أنني كذلك أيضًا.
If that's why you come here,
إذا كان هذا هو السبب الذي جعلك تأتي إلى هنا،
I find it uncomfortable.
أجد الأمر غير مريح.
Did you like it that much that day?
هل اعجبتك كثيرا في ذلك اليوم؟
Of course, I liked it, too.
بالطبع، أعجبني ذلك أيضًا.
I think I could sleep with you again.
أعتقد أنني أستطيع النوم معك مرة أخرى.
But not three times.
ولكن ليس ثلاث مرات.
It'd feel like we're something, then.
سوف نشعر وكأننا شيء ما حينها.
I don't want that.
انا لا اريد ذلك
What do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
Oppa.
أوه.
Why did you come all the way here?
لماذا أتيت إلى هنا كل هذه المسافة؟
Because I couldn't reach you.
لأنني لم أستطع الوصول إليك.
Oppa,
أوبا،
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
I must've been crazy that day.
لابد أنني كنت مجنونًا في ذلك اليوم.
I know you're friendly and sweet.
أعرف أنك ودود ولطيف.
I got jealous because I like you so much.
لقد شعرت بالغيرة لأنني أحبك كثيرًا.
And you suggested breaking up so easily?
واقترحت الانفصال بسهولة؟
- Huh? - Eun Hee,
- هاه؟ - يون هي،
you date someone to be happy.
تواعد شخصًا ما لتكون سعيدًا.
To be happier as two than alone.
أن نكون أكثر سعادة معًا من أن نكون بمفردنا.
But you felt jealous and anxious being with me.
لكنك شعرت بالغيرة والقلق من وجودك معي.
You think I was happy seeing you like that?
هل تعتقد أنني كنت سعيدًا برؤيتك بهذه الطريقة؟
I won't be like that anymore.
لن أكون هكذا بعد الآن.
Please reconsider just once.
يرجى إعادة النظر مرة واحدة فقط.
Please?
لو سمحت؟
When you said you liked me,
عندما قلت أنك معجب بي،
I didn't check twice.
لم أتحقق مرتين.
It's the same with the breakup.
إنه نفس الشيء مع الانفصال.
If it was off once, it's off.
إذا تم إيقافه مرة واحدة، فهو مغلق.
And don't come to see me like this again.
ولا تأتي لرؤيتي بهذه الطريقة مرة أخرى.
It makes me feel uncomfortable.
إنه يجعلني أشعر بعدم الارتياح.
Oppa.
أوه.
Oppa!
أوه!
[Sulo: A new post from Sulo]
[سولو: منشور جديد من سولو]
Yes.
نعم.
If it was off once, it's off.
إذا تم إيقافه مرة واحدة، فهو مغلق.
This isn't like me.
هذا لا يشبهني.
Are you Mr. Yun Ji Wu?
هل أنت السيد يون جي وو؟
Yes, I'm Yun Ji Wu.
نعم، أنا يون جي وو.
You're Su Jeong, right?
أنت سو جونغ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, I am.
نعم أنا.
Have a seat.
خذ مقعدا.
I'm sorry. I'm a bit late.
أنا آسف لقد تأخرت قليلاً.
Three minutes is nothing.
ثلاث دقائق ليست شيئا.
Thanks to that, I was practicing smiling
بفضل ذلك، كنت أمارس الابتسامة
trying to relax.
محاولة الاسترخاء.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
لم تأكل بعد، أليس كذلك؟
I asked them
سألتهم
and they recommend the lobster pasta.
ويوصون بمعكرونة جراد البحر.
Oh, lobster?
أوه، جراد البحر؟
I prepared a lobster dish per person.
لقد قمت بإعداد طبق جراد البحر لكل شخص.
Do you not like it or
هل لا يعجبك ذلك أم لا
are you allergic?
هل أنت مصاب بالحساسية؟
No, I like it.
لا، أنا أحب ذلك.
Should we get this?
هل يجب علينا الحصول على هذا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
♫ You and me ♫
♫ أنت وأنا ♫
♫ That one day we met ♫
♫ ذلك اليوم الذي التقينا فيه ♫
♫ I'm standing in front of you like this ♫
♫ أنا أقف أمامك هكذا ♫
♫ And you're looking at me ♫
♫ وأنت تنظر إلي ♫
You learned about relationships this way.
لقد تعلمت عن العلاقات بهذه الطريقة
No wonder you got dumped by your first love.
لا عجب أن تخلى عنك حبك الأول.
If an adult keeps reading stuff like this,
إذا استمر شخص بالغ في قراءة أشياء مثل هذه،
you'd keep getting dumped.
سوف تستمر في التعرض للإهمال.
You'd get dumped forever.
سيتم التخلي عنك إلى الأبد
♫ Will you acknowledge my heart? ♫
♫ هل ستعترف بقلبي؟ ♫
Who's going on a blind date?
من سيذهب في موعد أعمى؟
Team Leader is.
قائد الفريق هو
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
I asked if it was true.
سألت إذا كان هذا صحيحا.
Why do you want to know?
لماذا تريد أن تعرف؟
♫ The showering stars and the round moon ♫
♫ النجوم المتساقطة والقمر المستدير ♫
♫ I wish while wondering more ♫
♫ أتمنى بينما أتساءل أكثر ♫
We both have the worst first loves.
كلا منا لديه أسوأ الحب الأول.
Should we say cheers?
هل يجب علينا أن نقول هتافات؟
Cheers.
شكرا.
♫ It's shining on you, tell me now ♫
♫ إنه يشرق عليك، أخبرني الآن ♫
♫ Our bright night ♫
♫ ليلتنا المشرقة ♫
♫ We stay bright ♫
♫ نحن نبقى مشرقين ♫
♫ Stay bright all around ♫
♫ ابق مشرقًا في كل مكان ♫
I wonder if a stage
أتساءل عما إذا كانت المرحلة
would be good for the lounge area.
سيكون جيدا لمنطقة الصالة.
If we get a popular artist,
إذا حصلنا على فنان مشهور،
it'd help attract new customers.
سوف يساعد ذلك في جذب عملاء جدد.
It'd be entertaining to the current customers, too.
وسيكون الأمر مسليًا للعملاء الحاليين أيضًا.
If we did a live streaming of the show,
إذا قمنا ببث مباشر للعرض،
it'd help with the promotion, too.
وسوف يساعد ذلك في الترويج أيضًا.
I'd also like to use it for the
وأود أيضا استخدامه ل
renewal project promotion.
تعزيز مشروع التجديد.
Would you be available?
هل ستكون متاحة؟
Yes, I'd be available.
نعم، سأكون متاحًا.
Deputy, am I the only one who's cold?
نائبي، هل أنا الوحيد الذي يشعر بالبرد؟
No, I'm freezing, too.
لا، أنا أشعر بالبرد أيضًا
Any other suggestions?
أي اقتراحات أخرى؟
- No. - That's all, then.
- لا. - هذا كل شيء إذن.
Su Jeong!
سو جونغ!
Director Ban.
المخرج بان.
Why don't you get in?
لماذا لا تدخل؟
You said you could be late.
قلت أنك قد تتأخر.
But you're off early.
لكنك غادرت مبكرا.
Yes, thankfully.
نعم، ولله الحمد.
Shall we go, then?
هل نذهب إذن؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'll award the plaque of appreciation next.
سأقدم لوحة التقدير لاحقًا.
Here's Director Ban Ju Yeon of.
وهنا المخرج بان جو يون من.
Yongsung Department Store
متجر يونغسونغ
who donated the highest amount last year.
من تبرع بأعلى مبلغ في العام الماضي؟
Thank you so much for caring for the children
شكرا جزيلا على اهتمامكم بالأطفال
who needs help after losing their family.
من يحتاج إلى المساعدة بعد فقدان عائلته؟
Next is a performance from the violinist Yu Ri Ah,
التالي هو أداء من عازفة الكمان يو ري آه،
one of our scholarship students.
أحد طلاب المنح الدراسية لدينا.
When did you make time to do something so nice?
متى وجدت الوقت للقيام بشيء لطيف كهذا؟
You're so impressive.
أنت مثيرة للإعجاب للغاية.
Yongsung must have no worries.
لا بد أن يونغسونغ لا يشعر بالقلق.
You have such a great successor.
لديك خليفة عظيم.
Don't you agree?
ألا توافقني الرأي؟
Of course, Gureum Constructions has him, too.
بالطبع، شركة Gureum Constructions تمتلكه أيضًا.
Who said that?
من قال ذلك؟
- Pardon? - Who said
- عفواً؟ - من قال؟
my successor is Director Ban Ju Yeon here?
خليفتي هنا هو المخرج بان جو يون؟
Of course, because he's your only grandson.
بالطبع، لأنه حفيدك الوحيد.
I raised Yongsung like a child.
لقد ربّيت يونغسونغ مثل طفل.
No one can just become a successor
لا يمكن لأحد أن يصبح خليفة فقط
unless they can do as good of a job.
ما لم يتمكنوا من القيام بعمل جيد.
Only my late son could have.
فقط ابني الراحل كان بإمكانه فعل ذلك.
For the sake of the company,
من أجل الشركة،
I'm even considering
أنا حتى أفكر
hiring a management specialist.
تعيين متخصص في الإدارة.
Of course,
بالطبع،
Director Ban has been doing a great job.
لقد قام المخرج بان بعمل عظيم.
So, I'm thinking of exposing him to the media, too.
لذا، أفكر في عرضه على وسائل الإعلام أيضًا.
I'll let them know he's my grandson, too.
سأخبرهم أنه حفيدي أيضًا.
Oh, I see.
أوه، أرى.
Congratulations.
مبروك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Once your face is exposed,
بمجرد أن يتم الكشف عن وجهك،
you'll have to pay more attention to your behavior.
سيتعين عليك الاهتمام أكثر بسلوكك.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'll keep that in mind.
سأضع ذلك في الاعتبار.
♫ The new sun will rise again today ♫
♫ ستشرق الشمس الجديدة مرة أخرى اليوم ♫
♫ A different day from yesterday will start ♫
♫  سيبدأ يوم مختلف عن الأمس ♫
Does the Chairwoman allow you to drink?
هل تسمح لك رئيسة اللجنة بالشرب؟
Hey, what...
مهلا، ماذا...
You're scary when you stare like that.
أنت مخيف عندما تنظر هكذا.
What? Will you screw me over again?
ماذا؟ هل ستخدعني مرة أخرى؟
You can't. The Chairwoman is still here.
لا يمكنك ذلك، فالرئيسة لا تزال هنا.
What if you cause trouble
ماذا لو تسببت في مشكلة؟
and failed to inherit the company?
وفشل في وراثة الشركة؟
You've been humoring the old lady all your life
لقد كنت تتصرف مع السيدة العجوز طوال حياتك
cowering yourself at her mercy.
تخشى أن تخضع لرحمتها.
Haven't you? Huh?
ألم تفعل ذلك؟ هاه؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Hey.
يا.
Since I got to see it for the first time in a while,
منذ أن رأيته للمرة الأولى منذ فترة،
it was such a blast.
لقد كان انفجارا كبيرا.
Ju Yeon,
جو يون،
I realized why you live like such a loser.
لقد أدركت لماذا تعيش مثل هذا الخاسر.
I suddenly realized it. Really.
لقد أدركت ذلك فجأة. حقا.
You're the loser.
أنت الخاسر.
Me? Me?
ميمي؟
Why is that?
لماذا هذا؟
You don't know how to read the room.
أنت لا تعرف كيفية قراءة الغرفة.
I'm in a terrible mood right now.
أنا في مزاج رهيب الآن.
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
The Chairwoman also taught me to squash
كما علمتني رئيسة اللجنة كيفية السحق
anyone who provokes.
كل من يستفز.
Didn't you see your father wagging his tail at me?
ألم ترى والدك يهز ذيله في وجهي؟
I'm trying to teach you, but you can't learn.
أحاول أن أعلمك ، ولكنك لا تستطيع التعلم.
What am I supposed to do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
There's a very famous cafe here.
هناك مقهى مشهور جدًا هنا.
They're from Italy.
إنهم من إيطاليا.
This is the only store that has it.
هذا هو المتجر الوحيد الذي يتوفر فيه.
I know. I've always wanted to try it, too.
أعرف ذلك، لقد أردت دائمًا تجربته أيضًا.
You should've told me.
كان ينبغي عليك أن تخبرني.
This is your workplace.
هذا مكان عملك .
I didn't think you'd want to come after work.
لم أكن أعتقد أنك ترغب في المجيء بعد العمل.
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
Visiting often as a customer helps, too.
إن الزيارة المتكررة كعميل تساعد أيضًا.
Even better to hear a real customer's opinions.
ومن الأفضل أن نسمع آراء العملاء الحقيقيين.
Were you here for work, not a date?
هل كنت هنا للعمل وليس لموعد؟
I heard their dessert is good, too.
سمعت أن حلوياتهم جيدة أيضًا.
Do you like sweets?
هل تحب الحلويات؟
Yes, I eat everything bitter or sweet.
نعم، أنا آكل كل شيء مر أو حلو.
You like both.
أنت تحب كلاهما.
Do you not like that I eat everything?
هل لا يعجبك أن آكل كل شيء؟
Does it look like I have no taste?
هل يبدو الأمر وكأنني لا أملك أي ذوق؟
No. I like that you aren't picky.
لا. يعجبني أنك لست صعب الإرضاء.
It's so delicious.
إنه لذيذ جداً.
I can see why they're famous.
أستطيع أن أرى لماذا هم مشهورون.
I'm glad to hear that.
يسعدني سماع ذلك.
You're such a great person.
أنت شخص عظيم حقًا.
I wonder why you haven't had a boyfriend.
أتساءل لماذا لم يكن لديك صديق.
- Me? - Yes.
-أنا؟ -نعم.
By chance, were your standards very high?
بالصدفة، هل كانت معاييرك عالية جدًا؟
Rather than seeing just anyone,
بدلا من رؤية أي شخص،
I preferred to be alone. It's easier.
فضلت أن أكون وحدي، فهذا أسهل.
I'm more surprised by you.
أنا متفاجئ بك أكثر.
You must be popular.
يجب أن تكون مشهورًا.
You think so?
هل تعتقد ذلك؟
I've actually been waiting for someone like you.
لقد كنت في الواقع أنتظر شخصًا مثلك.
That was cheesy.
كان ذلك جبنيًا.
That's why I've been single.
لهذا السبب كنت عازبا.
Su Jeong, if you don't mind,
سو جونغ، إذا كنت لا تمانع،
can I do some shopping while I'm here?
هل يمكنني التسوق أثناء وجودي هنا؟
I needed some clothes.
كنت بحاجة إلى بعض الملابس.
I think you'd pick a good one for me.
أعتقد أنك ستختار واحدة جيدة بالنسبة لي.
Okay, sounds good.
حسنًا، يبدو جيدًا.
♫ You in my eyes ♫
♫ أنت في عيني ♫
♫ Your eyes are piercing me ♫
♫ عيناك تخترقني ♫
♫ And I'm crying bloody tears for you ♫
♫ وأنا أبكي دموعًا دموية من أجلك ♫
♫ Go away. Be gone. ♫
♫ اذهب بعيدا. اذهب بعيدا. ♫
♫ Your smile is so fake ♫
♫ ابتسامتك مزيفة للغاية ♫
♫ There will be no second chance ♫
♫ لن تكون هناك فرصة ثانية ♫
This is my last chance to enjoy the outside world.
هذه فرصتي الأخيرة للاستمتاع بالعالم الخارجي.
But why
ولكن لماذا
isn't it fun?
أليس هذا ممتعا؟
♫ There will be no second chance ♫
♫ لن تكون هناك فرصة ثانية ♫
♫ Go away. Be gone. ♫
♫ اذهب بعيدا. اذهب بعيدا. ♫
It's not like that.
ليس الأمر كذلك.
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
Seriously. What man?
بجدية، أي رجل؟
Why would I suddenly see him as a man?
لماذا أراه فجأة رجلاً؟
He's not a man. He's the same age as Su Bin.
إنه ليس رجلاً، إنه في نفس عمر سو بين
How could I think of him as a man?
كيف يمكنني أن أفكر فيه كرجل؟
Ridiculous.
سخيف.
If you're young, you're not a man?
إذا كنت شابًا، فأنت لست رجلاً؟
What about me? What's wrong with me?
ماذا عني؟ ما الخطأ فيّ؟
She has poor taste.
إنها ذات ذوق سيء.
But
لكن
why do I find Baek Su Jeong pretty?
لماذا أجد بايك سو جونغ جميلًا؟
Why do you keep looking down on me?
لماذا تستمر في النظر إلي باستخفاف؟
When did I?
متى فعلت ذلك؟
How's this one?
كيف هذا؟
It's simple. I think it'd suit you.
إنه أمر بسيط، أعتقد أنه يناسبك.
That's nice. I like it.
هذا جميل، أنا أحبه.
The size is...
الحجم هو...
- Just one moment. - Sure.
- لحظة واحدة فقط. - بالتأكيد.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Director.
مخرج.
You can't be here looking like that.
لا يمكنك أن تكون هنا وتبدو بهذا الشكل.
You've tried so hard to hide that.
لقد حاولت جاهدا إخفاء ذلك.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I know this is crazy, too, but
أعرف أن هذا جنون أيضًا، لكن
- But why are you here- - I remember everything.
- ولكن لماذا أنت هنا؟ - أتذكر كل شيء.
That was
كان ذلك
my first kiss.
قبلتي الاولى.
Gosh, why won't it open?
يا إلهي، لماذا لا يفتح؟
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
How strange.
كم هو غريب.
[My Dearest Nemesis]
[عدوتي العزيزة]
[We thank Park Jeong Ja for the special appearance]
[نشكر بارك جونغ جا على الظهور الخاص]
♫ To be honest, I don't know, oh, no ♫
♫ بصراحة، لا أعرف، أوه، لا ♫
♫ I think I'm losing my mind ♫
♫ أعتقد أنني أفقد عقلي ♫
♫ Oh, my gosh ♫
♫ يا إلهي ♫
♫ Like this ♫
♫ أعجبني هذا ♫
♫ What to do? I don't know ♫
♫ ماذا أفعل؟ لا أعرف ♫
♫ Keep falling to love, oh, tonight ♫
♫ استمر في الوقوع في الحب، أوه، الليلة ♫
♫ Shine a light on my heart ♫
♫ أشرق نورًا على قلبي ♫
Does he want an office romance or something?
هل يريد علاقة رومانسية في المكتب أم ماذا؟
I don't apologize for kissing.
لا أعتذر عن التقبيل
Because it wasn't a mistake.
لأنه لم يكن خطأ
I don't like younger men.
أنا لا أحب الرجال الأصغر سنا
And I hate his strange taste.
وأنا أكره ذوقه الغريب.
Why does she keep avoiding me?
لماذا تستمر في تجنبي؟
Study? What's in there?
الدراسة؟ ماذا يوجد هناك؟
Everything I liked was a secret.
كل ما أعجبني كان سرا
Are you in there, Director?
هل أنت هناك يا مدير؟
I think I'd be okay as long as I have you.
أعتقد أنني سأكون بخير طالما أنني أمتلكك.
I like you.
أنا معجب بك
♫ I approach you little by little ♫
♫ أقترب منك شيئا فشيئا ♫
♫ I put a spell on you secretly ♫
♫ لقد وضعت تعويذة عليك سراً ♫
♫ Stay on. Hold on. The end of this game ♫
♫ استمر. انتظر. نهاية هذه اللعبة ♫